<language>
    <group name="Options" prefix="options.">
        <str id="selectCategory">Select a category</str>

        <group name="Sections" prefix="sections.">
            <str id="controls">Controls</str>
            <str id="gameplay">Gameplay</str>
            <str id="graphicsandvisuals">Graphics and Visuals</str>
            <str id="languages">Languages</str>
            <str id="miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</str>
            <str id="debug">Debug</str>
        </group>

        <group name="Gameplay" prefix="gameplay.">
            <str id="volumeGlobal-name">Global Volume</str>
            <str id="volumeGlobal-desc">Changes the volume of the whole game.</str>

            <str id="volumeMusic-name">Music Volume</str>
            <str id="volumeMusic-desc">Changes the volume of the music.</str>

            <str id="volumeSFX-name">Sound Effects' Volume</str>
            <str id="volumeSFX-desc">Changes the volume of the sound effects.</str>

            <str id="streamedMusic-name">Streamed Music</str>
            <str id="streamedMusic-desc">If checked, only musics will have streamed audio, ALSO freeing a LOT of memory with the downside of higher cpu usage if more audio are being streamed at once. Turning this off will consume a lot of memory, especially on longer songs. If you aren't sure, leave this on.</str>

            <str id="streamedVocals-name">Streamed Vocals</str>
            <str id="streamedVocals-desc">If checked, vocals will also be streamed if Streamed Music is checked, will impact the performance if the song uses alot of vocals. If you aren't sure, leave this off.</str>

            <str id="downscroll-name">Downscroll</str>
            <str id="downscroll-desc">If checked, notes will go from up to down instead of down to up, as if they're falling.</str>

            <str id="middlescroll-name">Middlescroll</str>
            <str id="middlescroll-desc">If checked, your notes will be centered, making the notes easier to read (for mobile users at least).</str>

            <str id="timeBar-name">Time Bar</str>
            <str id="timeBar-desc">If checked, will show a bar that tracks the current song position, as well as its percentage from completion.</str>

            <str id="strumsBG-name">StrumLines' Background</str>
            <str id="strumsBG-desc">Give the strumlines a semi-(or fully)-transparent background.</str>

            <str id="ghostTapping-name">Ghost Tapping</str>
            <str id="ghostTapping-desc">If unchecked, hitting any strum that has no note on it will cause a fake miss, it will only deplete your health and lower your score, but won't affect your rating.</str>

            <str id="songOffset-name">Song Offset</str>
            <str id="songOffset-desc">Changes the offset that songs should start with.</str>

            <str id="camZoomOnBeat-name">Zoom Camera on Beat</str>
            <str id="camZoomOnBeat-desc">If checked, the camera will zoom on each beat.</str>
        </group>

        <group name="Graphics and Visuals" prefix="graphicsandvisuals.">
            <str id="framerate-name">Framerate</str>
            <str id="framerate-desc">Pretty self explanatory, isn't it?</str>

            <str id="colorHealthBar-name">Colored Health Bar</str>
            <str id="colorHealthBar-desc">If unchecked, the game will use the orginal red and green health bar from the Base Game (also known as V-Slice).</str>

            <str id="gameplayShaders-name">Intensive Shaders</str>
            <str id="gameplayShaders-desc">If checked, songs that use shaders that have more impact on the framerate will be loaded. Leave unchecked for a smoother experience.</str>

            <str id="naughtyness-name">Sentitive Content</str>
            <str id="naughtyness-desc">If unchecked, blood, gore and strong language will be toned down.</str>

            <str id="flashingMenu-name">Flashing Lights</str>
            <str id="flashingMenu-desc">If unchecked, will make flashes less "flashy". Leave unchecked if you're sentitive to these.</str>

            <str id="lowMemoryMode-name">Low Memory Mode</str>
            <str id="lowMemoryMode-desc">If checked, will reduce the amount of detail each part of the mod has to reduce memory usage.</str>

            <str id="gpuOnlyBitmaps-name">GPU Sprite Storing</str>
            <str id="gpuOnlyBitmaps-desc">If checked, will store loaded bitmaps (or more known as sprites) in the GPU, heavily reducing memory usage.</str>

            <str id="autoPause-name">Pause on Unfocus</str>
            <str id="autoPause-desc">If checked, going to another window will pause the game.</str>
            <str id="autoPause-desc-mobile">If checked, opening the notification bar or going out of the game will pause it.</str>

            <str id="fastMenus-name">Quick Transitions</str>
            <str id="fastMenus-desc">If checked, transitions between menus will be faster.</str>
        </group>

        <group name="Language" prefix="language.">
            <str id="translator">Translation by: {0}</str>
            <str id="en">English</str>
            <str id="es">Spanish</str>
            <str id="fr">French</str>
            <str id="pt">Portuguese</str>
            <str id="ja">Japanese</str>
            <str id="ru">Russian</str>
            <str id="de">German</str>
            <str id="it">Italian</str>
            <str id="pl">Polish</str>
            <str id="vi">Vietnamese</str>
        </group>

        <group name="Miscellaneous" prefix="miscellaneous.">
            <str id="devMode-name">Developer Mode</str>
            <str id="devMode-desc">If checked, you will be able to access developer features like certain keybinds, editors, developer options, state reloads, console and more.</str>

            <str id="resetSaveData-name">Reset Save Data</str>
            <str id="resetSaveData-desc">Select this option to reset your saved data. This will remove all of your highscores as well as your progress on the mod (WARNING: WILL RESTART THE GAME).</str>
        </group>

        <group name="Debug" prefix="debug.">
            <str id="showConsole-name">Show Console</str>
            <str id="showConsole-desc">Select this option to show the debug console, which contains log information about the game and the mod.</str>

            <str id="editorsResizable-name">Resizable Editors</str>
            <str id="editorsResizable-desc">If checked, this will allow the editors to render beyond the base 1280x720 resolution of FNF (allowing for more detail and space...)</str>

            <str id="bypassEditorsResize-name">Bypass Editor Resize</str>
            <str id="bypassEditorsResize-desc">Disables the minimum resolution for resizing editors (Needs Resizable Editors To Be Enabled).</str>

            <str id="editorSFX-name">Editor Sound Effects</str>
            <str id="editorSFX-desc">If checked, will play sound effects when working on editors (ex: will play sfxs when checking checkboxes...)</str>

            <str id="editorCharterPrettyPrint-name">Chart Pretty Print</str>
            <str id="editorCharterPrettyPrint-desc">If checked, the saved files from the chart editor will be formatted to be easily viewable</str>

            <str id="editorCharacterPrettyPrint-name">Character Pretty Print</str>
            <str id="editorCharacterPrettyPrint-desc">If checked, the saved files from the character editor will be formatted to be easily viewable</str>

            <str id="editorStagePrettyPrint-name">Stage Pretty Print</str>
            <str id="editorStagePrettyPrint-desc">If checked, the saved files from the stage editor will be formatted to be easily viewable</str>

            <str id="intensiveBlur-name">Intensive Blur</str>
            <str id="intensiveBlur-desc">If checked, will use more intensive blur that may be laggier but look better.</str>

            <str id="charterAutoSaves-name">Editor Autosaves</str>
            <str id="charterAutoSaves-desc">If checked, this will autosave your files in the editor, with the settings listed below.</str>

            <str id="charterAutoSaveTime-name">Autosaving Time</str>
            <str id="charterAutoSaveTime-desc">This controls how often the editor will autosave your file (in seconds)</str>

            <str id="charterAutoSaveWarningTime-name">Save Warning Time</str>
            <str id="charterAutoSaveWarningTime-desc">This controls how long the editor will warn you before it autosaves (in seconds, 0 to disable)</str>

            <str id="charterAutoSavesSeparateFolder-name">Autosaves Folder</str>
            <str id="charterAutoSavesSeparateFolder-desc">If checked, this will autosave your file in a separate folder with a time stamp instead of overriding your current file. (song/autosaves/)</str>

            <str id="songOffsetAffectEditors-name">Offset in Charter</str>
            <str id="songOffsetAffectEditors-desc">If checked, this will enable the Song Offset option in the Chart Editor too.</str>
        </group>

        <group name="Warnings" prefix="warnings.">
            <str id="warning">Warning</str>

            <str id="bloodAndGore-name">Blood and Gore</str>
            <str id="bloodAndGore-text1">This mod shows a large amount of blood and gore and may not be suitable for some people</str>
            <str id="bloodAndGore-text2">Tone it down?</str>

            <str id="flashingLights-name">Flashing Lights</str>
            <str id="flashingLights-text1">This mod has a lot of bright flashes and some people may be sentitive to that</str>
            <str id="flashingLights-text2">Tone them down?</str>

            <str id="menuReload">The menu must be reloaded for the changes to apply!</str>
            <str id="pressSuffix">{0} to reload the menu.</str>

            <str id="language">WARNING: A new language has been set!</str>
            <str id="dev-on">WARNING: Developer mode has been activated!</str>
            <str id="dev-off">WARNING: Developer mode has been deactivated!</str>

            <str id="dataDeletion1">Are you sure you want to</str>
            <str id="dataDeletion2">delete ALL your saved data?</str>
            <str id="dataDeletion3">THIS CANNOT BE UNDONE!!!</str>
        </group>
    </group>
</language>